http://www.biomatik.com/pages/rss-syndication/privacy-policy.html

All
Enter catalog no. or keywords, e.g. cd70 elisa, rgs5 antibody
COVID-19 Products
Trusted by 10,000+ Scientists Since 2002. View Our Customer Testimonials, Selected Publications and 3,000+ Cited Publications at Google Scholar.
Biomatik PRIVACY POLICYLast Updated: 05/02/2019
Biomatik (“us”, “we”, or “our”) values your privacy. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our websites and the choices you have associated with that data.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEData Collected
1. Personal DataWhen you navigate our website or use our services, you may be asked to provide certain personal information that can be used to contact or identify you. This information may include, but is not limited to:
Email addressFirst name and last nameCountryInstitution/Company
How does Biomatik Use Your Personal Data?This personal data may be used to contact you with newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving these communications from Biomatik at any time by following the communication preference link in our emails or by contacting us. We will never sell your personal data.
2. Site AnalyticsWe may collect information on how you accessed and used our websites. This information may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, web browser use, location information, information accessed, time and date of visit, and other data.
How does Biomatik Use Site Analytics?Site analytics helps Biomatik better understand our audience and how they utilize our site. This information allows us to optimize our website for better user experience and create content tailored to your needs.
3. CookiesCookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows us or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the website more useful to you.
How Does Biomatik Use Cookies?
Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and see how visitors move around our websites. This helps us improve the way the websites work, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to our websites. This enables us to remember your information and auto-populate forms for you.Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to the websites, the pages you have visited, and the links you have followed. We use this information to make content displayed more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.
Third Party CookiesPlease note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we may or may not have any control. We suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.
For example, Google uses cookies to anonymously record that a user has clicked on a Google link that referred the user to any Biomatik website. For further information: https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or on our website, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
×
© 2002-2020 Biomatik All rights reserved
Site Map
|
Privacy Policy
© 2002-2020 Biomatik
Top
